const quiz3data = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: "This is the first question on Conditionals 3 page.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "A. red", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "B. green", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ""
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: "when it ___, I always ___ the bus.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "rains / take ", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: " will rain  / take", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use Zero Conditional when the result will always happen and we are talking in general. The structure is: ",
      help1: " if + present simple, present simple"
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: "If you place this order now, you ___ it by noon tomorrow.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "will receive", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "receive", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "When there is a real possibility that this condition will happen we use first conditional. The structure is:  ",
      help1: "if + present simple , will + infinitive"
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ""
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: "If you ___ to visit the iconic Wembley Stadium, ___ a ticket.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "want / buy", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "wanted / will buy", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "We use Zero Conditional to give instructions or to tell people what to do. The structure is: ",
      help1: " if + present simple, present simple"
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: "If I ___ your card, I ___ give it back to you.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "find / will", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "found / will", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "When there is a real possibility that this condition will happen we use first conditional. The structure is:  ",
      help1: "if + present simple , will + infinitive"
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ""
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ""
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: "I ___ tell Maria to phone you if I ___ her.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "will / see", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "will have / saw", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: "When there is a real possibility that this condition will happen we use first conditional. The structure is:  ",
      help1: "if + present simple , will + infinitive"
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ""
    },
    {
      id: 11,
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
      ],
      help: ""
    },
    {
      id: 12,
      question: "What ___ you do if it ___ tomorrow?",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "do / is snowing", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "will / snows", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: "When there is a real possibility that this condition will happen we use first conditional. we are talking about one particular situation, not in general. The structure is:  ",
      help1: "if + present simple , will + infinitive"
    },
    
]

export default quiz3data